<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Celerity</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="place_the_r">
Place the Rectangle area as on Vehicle Reg plate as shown in the image The app will automatically detect and capture the registration number upon recognition
</string>
    <string name="location">location\n</string>
    <string name="away">away</string>
    <string name="swipe_for_v">Swipe For Vehicle Reg No.</string>
    <string name="key_chain_confirmation_alert">Key Chain Confirmation Alert</string>
    <string name="keeping_you">"Keeping your vehicle safe and secure from theft of your vehicle or parcels is an important part of being a delivery driver. 90% of all vehicle thefts are when drivers leave their vehicle unattended unlocked or leave their keys in the vehicle. You as the Responsible Delivery Driver need to be aware of your responsibility and care of duty. Driver safety is important to us and we advise any driver that is threatened with violence for their vehicle and its contents to walk away from your vehicle and if your keys are taken to contact OSM immediately and contact the police and report the incident.\nPlease remember that mistakes mean £££ when not wearing your key chain. "</string>
    <string name="tick_to_ack">Tick to acknowledge that I have been instructed on keeping my vehicle safe and secure and that my Keychain willl be used at all times while making deliveries.</string>
    <string name="ana_carolin">Ana Carolina Souza Dos Santos</string>
    <string name="dxm4">DMX4\n</string>
    <string name="vehicle_mil">Vehicle Mileage\n</string>
    <string name="previous_re">Previous Recorded Mileage</string>
    <string name="miles">320 MIles\n</string>
    <string name="route_name">Route Name</string>
    <string name="celerity_ls">Celerity LS Delivery Driver Training Record</string>
    <string name="observation">Observations and explanations must be conducted on a Nursery Level 1 route. The new driver should make at least 50 unassisted deliveries, before being considered as fully trained. Where an individual is identified as not ready the On Site Manager must be made aware of the concerns and the development path to competency before the individual will be allowed to take a route out on their own. All sections must be completed.</string>
</resources>